comtrust.ae 2005-04-03

# Privacy Policy

---  
  
Comtrust – a business unit of Emirates Telecommunications Corporation (Etisalat) that provides e-business solutions.  
  
Corporate Website - Internet Privacy Policy  
  
Comtrust respects your concerns about privacy and it is our endeavor and objective to provide excellent quality service to all our customers.  
This privacy policy has been formulated to help you understand the nature of the information we collect from you when you visit our website and how this personal information will be treated by us.  

Security  
  
Comtrust website pages that request submission of personal information and credit card information are secured by 128 bit encryption to ensure security of your online transactions.  

Browsing  
  
Personal information collected online for subscriptions, renewals, inquiries or otherwise will be used for the sole purpose of processing your subscriptions or inquiries and will not be given to any organization or individual outside of Etisalat.  

Internet Protocol (IP) Address   
  
Whenever you visit our Corporate Website, the server used by our Web Host will make a record of your IP Address, the date and time of your visit, the type of Internet Browser you use and the URL of any web site which referred you to our web site.  

Web Surveys  
  
Our online web surveys enable us to gather specific information regarding issues such as your feedback on the look and feel of our website. Additionally we may also request information on several elements of our Customer Service. Your feedback is vital, appreciated and enables us to enhance the Quality of Customer Service we provide. The provision of your name and other details is totally optional unless otherwise specified.  

Links to other Web Sites   
  
Our website may contain links to other sites for your convenience and information only. Comtrust is not responsible for the data collection practices, the privacy policies or the content of those websites that are accessible via a link from this site.   

Disclosure of Information   
  
Comtrust will maintain at all times the privacy and confidentiality of all personal information collected. Such information may only be disclosed when required by law or when in good faith we believe that such action is necessary or desirable to comply with the law, protect or defend the rights or property of Comtrst or its users.  

Information needed to execute the transactions you request  
  
When we do require information from you, we will request you to submit this to us voluntarily. This information will help us to get in touch with you and process your requests where applicable. The information can also be used for marketing or quality assurance purposes.  
The information you provide will never be sold to any third party for their own marketing purposes without your express permission in writing unless it is done on an aggregated basis for statistical purposes and research without any information which can be used to identify you.   

Contact Us with your Questions and Comments  
  
Information you provide will be treated as confidential. Online Forms request information to help us provide you with enhanced quality of customer care. Such information provided will be used to respond to your questions, comments or requests by either Comtrust or any of its business divisions and subsidiary companies only.  

Disclosure to Third Parties   
  
We will not sell, trade, rent or release any information to any third party outside Etisalat, its business divisions or its subsidiary companies. Disclosure may only be made upon an order from a Judicial or Regulatory Authority.  

Privacy Policy Changes  
  
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy Terms and Conditions as and when necessary and appropriate. All changes will be carried out here and you will always be informed of what information we gather, how we might use it and to whom we may disclose.  

Conclusion  
  
Your privacy concerns are important to us. Please contact [info@comtrust.ae](mailto:info@comtrust.ae) for any queries regarding our privacy policy.  

Home  |  Quality Policy  |  Privacy Policy  |  [Jobs](http://www.etisalat-careers.ae/)  |  Contact Us  
©2004 Comtrust. All Rights Reserved
